You can't Google experience. You can't Google
it. You have to go through it.
Early on in your career, you were primarily
in sales. How has the skills that you learned
from being a salesman translated and helped you own
a company of your own at such a young age?
Someone can teach you all the tricks, all
the cool things to say. You could dress perfect,
but until you've been told no, until you've
been cussed out, until you've been screamed at,
until you have people tell you no after
no after no, and you still have to have
that same attitude and still be able to deliver
the message the right way, you won't get it.
There's no textbook that can teach it. When
you're in sales and you learn how to communicate
to all different types of
people, different ethnicities, different backgrounds, different
ages, different experiences, you have
no choice but to get better.